let questions3 = [
	{
			numb: 1,
			question: "When is the creation of Ethernet?.",
			answer: "C. 1973",
			options: [
				"A. 1972",
				"B. 1970",
				"C. 1973",
				"D. 1969"
			]
	},
	
    {
	numb: 2,
			question: 
			"This identifies the frame's data originating NIC or interface.",
			answer: "A. Source MAC Address Field",
			options: [
				"A. Source MAC Address Field",
				"B. Length/Type Field",
				"C. Frame Check Sequence Field",
				"D. Data and Pad Fields"
			]
	},
	
    {
	numb: 3,
			question: "This contains the encapsulated data from a higher layer, which is generic Layer 3 PDU, or more commonly, and IPv4 packet.",
		 	answer: "D. Data and Pad Fields",
			options: [
				"A. Source MAC Address Field",
				"B. Length/Type Field",
				"C. Frame Check Sequence Field",
				"D. Data and Pad Fields"
			]
	},
	
    {
	numb: 4,
			question: 
			"A tool to examine the MAC address of our computer ?",
			answer: "C. ipconfig",
			options: [
				"A. ping",
				"B. hex",
				"C. ipconfig",
				"D. IPCONFIG"
			]
	},
	
    {
	numb: 5,
			question: 
			"In the CSMA/CD access method, all network devices that have messages to send must listen before transmitting. ",
			answer: "A. Carrier Sense",
			options: [
				"A. Carrier Sense",
				"B. Multi-Access",
				"C. Collision Detection",
				"D. Media Access"
			]
	},
	
    {
	numb: 6,
			question: 
			"A period of time is required for a bit to be placed and sensed on the media. This period of time is referred to as the bit time.",
			answer: "B. Bit Time",
			options: [
				"A. Slot Time",
				"B. Bit Time",
				"C. Timing",
				"D. Latency"
			]
	},
	
    {
	numb: 7,
			question: 
			"Four data rates are currently defined for operation over optical fiber and twisted-pair cables. Which one is NOT included?",
			answer: "D. 10,000 Gbps - 10 Gigabit Ethernet",
			options: [
				"A. 10 Mbps - 10Base-T Ethernet",
				"B. 100 Mbps - Fast Etherner",
				"C. 1000 Mbps - Gigabit Ethernet",
				"D. 10,000 Gbps - 10 Gigabit Ethernet"
			]
	},
	
    {
	numb: 8,
			question: "When device is in listening mode, it can detect when a collision occurs on the shared media.",
			answer: "C. Collision Detection",
			options: [
     		"A. Carrier Sense",
				"B. Multi-Access",
				"C. Collision Detection",
				"D. Media Access"
			]
	},
	
    {
	numb: 9,
			question: "This frame is used to detect errors in a frame. It uses a cyclic	redundancy check (CRC).",
			answer: "C. Frame Check Sequence Field",
			options: [
     		"A. Source MAC Address Field",
				"B. Length/Type Field",
				"C. Frame Check Sequence Field",
				"D. Data and Pad Fields"
			]
	},
	
    {
	numb: 10,
			question: "Where data can only travel in one direction at once, this time becomes an important parameter in determining how many devices can share a network",
			answer: "A. Slot Time",
			options: [
				"A. Slot Time",
				"B. Bit Time",
				"C. Timing",
				"D. Latency"
			]
	}
];